<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Travel App</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string name="head_1">The Roman Colosseum</string>
    <string name="head_2">The Great Wall of China</string>
    <string name="head_3">The Taj Mahal</string>
    <string name="head_4">Christ the Redeemer</string>
    <string name="head_5">Machu Picchu</string>
    <string name="head_6">Chicén Itzá</string>
    <string name="head_7">Petra</string>

    <string name="desc_1">The Colosseum, also known as the Flavian Amphitheatre, is a large amphitheater located in the center of Rome, Italy. It was built during the Roman Empire, around 70-80 AD, and is considered one of the greatest examples of Roman architecture and engineering.\n\n

The Colosseum is oval in shape, with a total circumference of about 545 meters (1,788 feet) and stands 50 meters (164 feet) tall. It was built to accommodate tens of thousands of spectators, who would watch a variety of events, including gladiator battles, animal hunts, and plays. It was constructed using concrete and stone, and features a complex system of arches, vaults, and tunnels that supported its weight and allowed for the movement of people and animals.\n\n

The Colosseum has a distinctive exterior, with four tiers of arches adorned with Corinthian columns. The interior of the Colosseum is divided into two main levels, the arena floor and the upper level, which were separated by a wall known as the velarium. The arena floor was made of wood and was surrounded by a moat, which could be filled with water for naval battles or animal hunts. The upper level, or the cavea, was divided into sections and was used by spectators to watch the events below.\n\n

Today, the Colosseum is one of the most popular tourist attractions in Rome, and is a UNESCO World Heritage Site. It is a symbol of the power and grandeur of the Roman Empire, and serves as a reminder of the rich history and cultural heritage of Rome and Italy.</string>

    <string name="desc_2">The Great Wall of China is a series of fortifications that were built, rebuilt, and maintained over the centuries to protect and defend the Chinese Empire from invasions and raids by nomadic groups. The wall stretches more than 13,000 miles (21,000 kilometers) across northern China, from the Yellow Sea in the east to the Gobi Desert in the west, making it the longest wall in the world.\n\n

The Great Wall was built using a variety of materials, including brick, tamped earth, and stone, and features a series of watchtowers, garrison stations, and beacon towers that were used to communicate and defend against invaders. It was constructed over a period of more than 2,000 years, with the earliest sections dating back to the 7th century BC.\n\n

The Great Wall was designated as a UNESCO World Heritage Site in 1987, and it is one of the most famous landmarks in China and the world. It is also a popular tourist attraction, with many people visiting to walk along its length and see the breathtaking views it offers.\n\n

Despite its impressive size and historical significance, the Great Wall of China is not visible from space, as is often believed. It is, however, visible from the moon with the naked eye, due to its long length and the fact that it was built along the crest of a series of hills and mountains.
</string>

    <string name="desc_3">The Taj Mahal is a mausoleum located in Agra, India. It was built by Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan in memory of his favorite wife, Mumtaz Mahal, who died during childbirth in 1631. The Taj Mahal is considered one of the most beautiful and iconic buildings in the world, and it is a UNESCO World Heritage Site.\n\n

The Taj Mahal is made of white marble and is set in formal gardens on the south bank of the Yamuna River. It is considered a masterpiece of Mughal architecture, which combines elements of Indian, Persian, and Islamic styles. The building is symmetrical and features an intricate inlay of precious and semiprecious stones, including jade, lapis lazuli, amethyst, and crystal.\n\n

The Taj Mahal is a popular tourist destination and attracts millions of visitors each year. It is also a symbol of love and devotion, and it is often referred to as the "jewel of Muslim art in India."</string>

    <string name="desc_4">x</string>
    <string name="desc_5">x</string>
    <string name="desc_6">x</string>
    <string name="desc_7">x</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>